A Guide to the Records of the Arlington County Civic Federation, 1928-2008
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Activities
  - Subject Files, 1943-1988
    - Republican Party of Virginia Handbook for Mass Meetings, Conventions and Parties, 1999 (Box 30)
    - Rodent Facts (Box 30)
    - Roundtable, 1995-2000 (Box 30)
    - Schools, 1999-2000 (Box 31)
    - Stadium, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Traffic Calming, 1998-2000 (Box 31)
    - Virginia Baseball Handbook, 2002 (Box 31)
    - Banquet, 1995-1996 (Box 31)
    - Banquet, 1997-1998 (Box 31)
    - Banquet, 1999-2000 (Box 31)
    - Banquet, 2003 (Box 31)
    - Banquet, 2006-2007 (Box 31)
    - Banquet, 2007-2008 (Box 31)
    - Candidates Meeting/Nights, 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Candidates Meeting/Nights, 2000, 2001 (Box 31)
    - County Fair, 2004, 2007 (Box 31)
    - Legislative Issues, 1988, 1997-1999 (Box 31)
  - Chronological Reading Files, 1942-1981
    - 1942-1948 (Box 31)
    - 1949-1955 (Box 31)
    - 1958-1961 (Box 32)
    - 1962 (Box 32)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 32)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 32)
    - 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 32)
    - 1972 (Box 32)
    - 1973 (Box 32)
    - 1974 (Box 32)
    - 1975 (Box 32)
    - 1976 (Box 32)
    - 1976 (Box 33)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 33)
    - 1979 (Box 33)
    - 1980 (Box 33)
    - 1981 (Box 33)
  - Annual Banquet Files
    - 1958-1961 (Box 33)
    - 1969 (Box 33)
    - 1970 (Box 33)
    - 1971 (Box 33)
    - 1972 (Box 33)
    - 1973 (Box 33)
    - 1974 (Box 33)
    - 1975 (Box 33)
    - 1976 (Box 33)
    - 1977 (Box 33)
    - 1978 (Box 33)
    - 1979 (Box 34)
    - 1980 (Box 34)
    - 1981 (Box 34)
    - 1982 (Box 34)
    - 1983 (Box 34)
    - 1984 (Box 34)
    - 1985 (Box 34)
    - 1986 (Box 34)
    - 1987 (Box 34)
    - 1996 (Box 34)
  - Correspondence
    - July 1995 - June 1996 (Box 34)
    - November 1996 - May 1997 (Box 34)
    - June - November 1997 (Box 34)
    - July 1998 - May 1999 (Box 34)
    - January - March 2000 (Box 34)
    - June 2000 - May 2001 (Box 34)
    - August 2001 - June 2002 (Box 34)
    - February 2004 (Box 34)
    - August 2004 - March 2005 (Box 34)
    - September 2005 - June 2006 (Box 34)
    - August 2006 - July 2007 (Box 34)
    - November 2007 - March 2008 (Box 34)
- Outreach
  - ACCF Bulletins
    - 1944-1953 (Box 34)
    - Civic News, 1998, 1999 (Box 34)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 34)
    - 1956 (Box 34)
    - 1957 (Box 34)
    - 1958 (Box 34)
    - 1959 (Box 34)
    - 1960 (Box 34)
    - 1961 (Box 34)
    - 1982 (Box 34)
    - 1963 (Box 34)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - 1966 (Box 34)
    - 1967 (Box 35)
    - 1968 (Box 35)
    - 1969 (Box 35)
    - 1970 (Box 35)
    - 1971 (Box 35)
    - 1972 (Box 35)
    - 1973 (Box 35)
    - 1974 (Box 35)
    - 1975 (Box 35)
    - 1976 (Box 35)
    - 1977 (Box 35)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 35)
    - 1980 (Box 35)
    - 1981 (Box 35)
    - 1982 (Box 35)
    - 1983 (Box 35)
    - 1984 (Box 35)
    - 1985 (Box 35)
    - 1986 (Box 35)
    - 1987 (Box 35)
    - No date (Box 35)
    - 1985, 1988, 1993, 1995 (Box 35)
    - "Better Government," October 23, 1930 (Box 35)
    - "Civic News," 1994, 1995 (Box 35)
  - Newspaper Clippings
    - 1943-1963 (Box 35)
    - 1980-1983 (Box 35)
  - Civic Month Ephemera
    - 1968 (Box 35)
  - ACCF History
    - 1972-1985 (Box 35)
  - Photographs
    - Unidentified photographs, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Stationery Samples
    - Samples, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Ephemera
    - Ephemera (Box 35)
    - Robert's Rules of Order, rebinding, 1968 (Box 35)
  - ACCF Newsletter
    - September 1995 - June 1997 (Box 35)
    - September 1997 - December 1998 (Box 36)
    - 1999 (Box 36)
    - January - June 2000 (Box 36)
  - "The Civic Voice"
    - September 2000 - December 2001 (Box 36)
    - January 2002 - June 2003 (Box 36)
    - September 2003 - June 2005 (Box 36)
- Office of the Secretary, Tommye Morton
  - December 1986 (Box 36)
  - Index 1987-1988 (Box 36)
  - January 1987 (Box 36)
  - February 1987 (Box 36)
  - March 1987 (Box 36)
  - April 1987 (Box 36)
  - May 1987 (Box 36)
  - June 1987 (Box 36)
  - September 1987 (Box 36)
  - October 1987 (Box 36)
  - November 1987 (Box 36)
  - December 1987 (Box 36)
  - Index 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - January 1988 (Box 36)
  - February 1988 (Box 36)
  - March 1988 (Box 36)
  - April 1988 (Box 36)
  - May 1988 (Box 36)
  - June 1988 (Box 36)
  - September 1988 (Box 36)
  - October 1988 (Box 36)
  - November 1988 (Box 36)
  - December 1988 (Box 36)
  - Index, 1988-1990; Delegate List, October 1989 (Box 36)
  - January 1989 (Box 36)
  - February 1989 (Box 36)
  - March 1989 (Box 36)
  - April 1989 (Box 36)
  - May 1989 (Box 36)
  - June 1989 (Box 37)
  - September 1989 (Box 37)
  - October 1989 (Box 37)
  - November 1989 (Box 37)
  - December 1989 (Box 37)
  - Index, 1990-1991; Delegate Lists, April 1990, April 1991 (Box 37)
  - January 1990 (Box 37)
  - February 1990 (Box 37)
  - March 1990 (Box 37)
  - April 1990 (Box 37)
  - May 1990 (Box 37)
  - June 1990 (Box 37)
  - September 1990 (Box 37)
  - October 1990 (Box 37)
  - November 1990 (Box 37)
  - December 1990 (Box 37)
  - Index, 1991-1992; Delegate Lists, June 1991, November 1991 (Box 37)
  - February 1991 (Box 37)
  - March 1991 (Box 37)
  - April 1991 (Box 37)
  - May 1991 (Box 37)
  - June 1991 (Box 37)
  - September 1991 (Box 37)
  - Octber 1991 (Box 37)
  - November 1991 (Box 37)
  - December 1991 (Box 37)
  - Index 1992-1993; Delegate List, November 1992 (Box 37)
  - January 1992 (Box 37)
  - February 1992 (Box 37)
  - March 1992 (Box 37)
  - April 1992 (Box 37)
  - May 1992 (Box 37)
  - June 1992 (Box 37)
  - September 1992 (Box 37)
  - October 1992 (Box 38)
  - November 1992 (Box 38)
  - December 1992 (Box 38)
  - Index, 1993-1994 Delegate List, November 1993 (Box 38)
  - January 1993 (Box 38)
  - February 1993 (Box 38)
  - March 1993 (Box 38)
  - April 1993 (Box 38)
  - May 1993 (Box 38)
  - June 1993 (Box 38)
  - September 1993 (Box 38)
  - October 1993 (Box 38)
  - November 1993 (Box 38)
  - December 1993 (Box 38)
  - Index, 1994-1995; Delegate List, December 1994 (Box 38)
  - January 1994 (Box 38)
  - February 1994 (Box 38)
  - March 1994 (Box 38)
  - April 1994 (Box 38)
  - May 1994 (Box 38)
  - June 1994 (Box 38)
  - September 1994 (Box 38)
  - October 1994 (Box 38)
  - November 1994 (Box 38)
  - December 1994 (Box 38)
  - January 1995 (Box 38)
  - February 1995 (Box 38)
  - March 1995 (Box 38)
  - April 1995 (Box 38)
  - May 1995 (Box 39)
  - June 1995 (Box 39)
- Financial Materials
  - Treasurer's Files
    - Treasurer's Files in bound ledger, 1961/1962 - 1992/1993 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 1993/1994 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 1994/1995 - 1995/1996 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 1996/1997 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 1997/1998 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 1998/1999 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 1999/2000 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2000/2001 (Box 39)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2001/2002 (Box 40)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2002/2003 (Box 40)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2003/2004 (Box 40)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2004/2005 (1) (Box 40)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2004/2005 (2) (Box 40)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2005/2006 (1) (Box 40)
    - Treasurer's Files, 2005/2006 (2) (Box 40)
- Arlington County Official Publications
  - Ad Hoc Committee Neighborhood Traffic Calming Interim Report, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Arlington Bicycle Transportation Plan, 1994 (Box 41)
  - Arlington County Pedestrian Transportation Plan, 1997 (Box 41)
  - Arlington County Proposed Budget v. 1 FY 2001 (1) (Box 41)
  - Arlington County Proposed Budget v. 1 FY 2001 (2) (Box 41)
  - Arlington County Proposed Budget v. 1 FY 2001 (3) (Box 41)
  - Arlington County Proposed Budget v. 2 FY 2001 (1) (Box 41)
  - Arlington County Proposed Budget v. 2 FY 2001 (2) (Box 41)
  - Chesapeake Bay Preservation, 1992 (Box 41)
  - Handbook of Planning Technology, 1997 (Box 41)
  - Master Transportation Plan, Part 1, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Open Space Master Plan, 1994 (Box 42)
  - Report of the Arlington County Human Services Commission, 1995 (Box 42)
  - Review of the Street Element of the Arlington County Comprehensive Plan, 2000 (Box 42)
  - Virginia Square Sector Plan, [1984?] (Box 42)
  - Virginia Square Sector Plan Draft, February 25, 2002 (Box 42)
  - Virginia Square Sector Plan Draft, April 10, 2002 (Box 42)
  - "Arlington County Civic Federation's Efforts to Create a Study Commission on City/County Form of Government, 1973-1978, submitted by John Steven Chwat" (Box 42)